Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
No mama, lots of time?
Sarah Fun, fun, fun, you so cool!
No, but,
Kill or kiss Let's go!
Kill or kiss, Kick, kill.
Let's go!
Kill or kiss, kick, kill
You in, Hamstermaster?
I say we go kick the
Beast Clan's ass together.
You sure you want me? You bet.
Would you mind lending me a hand?
Guess I'd better show you
what I'm really made of.
You heard him, my hammies.
Assemble.
Modified Bloodline++ star map.
Do your thing.
It's a map of the island.
I got my hammies to split up
and survey the area earlier.
That ought to come in handy.
We won't get lost finding the Beastmaster.
You think that's good?
Wait till you see what I've got in
store next Thank your lucky stars,
Hikaru Gator Here comes the
real treat My secret talent
I rarely break out for anyone
Making home-cooked meals
Thoughtful, but no thanks I don't
eat food I haven't made myself Away,
my hammies Bring nuts, berries,
and anything else that looks edible
Hey, hold on Modified bloodline plus-plus.
Black hole!
That doesn't sound edible.
It's complete!
It's the Arashiyama special.
I present Anything Gruul.
What?
Wait, I told you I can't have...
Just shut up and eat it.
You're gonna die without food.
Master Hikaru, any food served to you
by another person will be poisoned.
Therefore, you must never
let your guard down.
Even the slightest lapse in
judgment will result in death.
Wow, you were serious.
You don't have to...
Arashiyama, that was delicious.
I know, right?
And don't worry about the dirt in it.
For what it's worth, it
never made me queasy.
My big brother went missing a while ago.
Whenever we ran out of money
he used to whip me up a batch.
Do you do something special
when you're making it?
No tricks, I copy his recipe.
Although if anything was
different this time it might have
had something to do with me
thinking about you while making it.
Given your injuries I picked
out the healthiest nuts,
gave everything a nice subtle seasoning,
then stewed it so it'd be easier to eat.
So guess it was special.
I needed that. Thank you.
It's the best food I think I've ever had.
By the way those glasses
look a lot like mine.
If they do it's a total coincidence.
Nothing more.
Well, get a load of Prince Charming
coming out here to face us all on his own.
Prepare for pain at the
hands of the koala masters.
Please keep it down.
My client has had a pretty eventful day.
She needs to get her rest.
Giving us orders, even though
you're outnumbered, Sevenfold?
You really ought to be more
worried about yourself, mate.
Now witness the power bestowed upon
us by the Supreme Beastmaster, Bao!
Finally, a little peace and quiet.
We're safe for now.
Arashiyama!
You really like this crap?
Figured it'd be decent based
on how you slopped it down!
But it's trash and I have
to rinse my mouth out now.
Where is she?
What have you done with her?
Know what I slopped down?
Dating reality shows.
Every time when the main
couple starts getting
close some sleazebag butts in.
They're the ones I root for.
So I went and offed your lady.
Sorry,
man.
Hang on.
These glasses of hers, they
look just like your specs.
Disgusting to think one of
my pet sinking so low. Gotcha!
Did I go too far? Relax.
I didn't kill her.
At least not yet.
You asshole.
You've caught me in a rare mood, man!
See, I found a new kind of blood!
After a
little taste, I can't get enough!
This stuff's mind-blowing!
Did I mention it's yours?
The last puzzle piece I need
to perfect cross-sanguination.
The closer you get to dying, the more your
Your modified bloodline comes to life,
shutting down any risky rejection.
Meaning it lets me marry bloodlines that
would never mix otherwise risk-free.
Birdbrain managed to get
a small sample, R .I .P.
But I need more.
So would you shut up already and
start fighting for your life, Gato?
Get your head in the game!
Remember, I took your
potential bride-to-be!
So if you don't want me to kill
your lady friend, go and save her!
How about it feeling motivated huh?
Hey Gato dude!
Are you listening Earth to Gato?
Sweet there's that murderous
rage I was waiting for!
Glad to see you being a good sport!
That alone made the trip
worthwhile wouldn't you say?
Hurry up or the hamster chick's going
The way of the dodo, and I ain't kidding.
Damn it.
All these guys, they're
from the Beast Clan.
They're from branch families just like me.
I'd heard rumors about strange
disappearances at association meetings.
This explains it.
Good luck, Sirius.
I'm counting on you.
Toxin. Double dose.
That's what I'm talking about!
All you needed was a little push!
Gotta hand it to you.
No matter what anyone else says.
Out of our whole generation of masters,?
you're a prodigy.
Even the fodder I made
using my cross-sanguination,
there's no match for natural selection.
But let me ask,
what if you had to take
on a hundred of them?
Even an apex predator like
yourself ends up becoming prey.
At this point, it doesn't
come down to skill anymore.
Damn it.
Just a little further.
I can't give up after coming this far.
I could triple dose, but I'd probably
kill myself for good this time.
Master Higa, it's imperative you never
take risks that are beyond your abilities.
Even though you're fit to inherit the Poison
Clan, an overdose will still kill you.
You must go accustomed
to toxins gradually.
Ask yourself how it would
look if the future clan leader
died before achieving the
quintessence of The poison
master's art your purpose
in life should be to reach
that impossible pinnacle To
take the most lethal incurable
poison and survive an heir
to a main clan dying like
this Pathetic sure I buffed
them with cross sanguination
but they're small fries who
Ought to be ashamed to call
themselves masters and
they've got him dead to rights
more amateur work I see
you haven't changed mr.
Beastmaster I hope you're watching
you know Instead of hiring
a hundred amateurs you could have
entrusted your business to me.
Cost-wise it'd be far more
efficient don't you think Mr Ghetto?
Let's get one thing straight
you and I are not friends
I took a job offer from that
marriage advisor of yours
I figured you could use some
backup besides owing someone
a debt isn't exactly good
for business you're here to
help me so what embarrassing
amount did you ask for on
this high risk job 10 000
yen a day 10 000 you're from
one of the great families an
industry leader and here you
are driving down rates for
the rest of us professionals
that's just perfect go hire an accountant
because this couldn't be
any less cost effective
I'm fighting the Beast
Clan for the sake of
my cafe and to protect
any future customers.
But why are you two willing
to go this far for that woman?
Why are you dead set on helping her?
Personally, I'm just along for the ride.
As long as Gato can find a wife!
As long as he continues doing
jobs for people who need him?
He'll find the person he wants
to spend his life with, you know?
If the end goal is to get hitched,
I feel like there's got to be
better ways of going about it.
I mean, does it need to be so life or
death when there's matchmaking parties,
dating apps, and things like that?
You know, you might be right.
I wouldn't say that it's the most
efficient system for everyone out there.
But for Gato, I think it's the
best way for him to meet his match.
Save girls in a bind and
make them fall for you.
We'll call it Operation White Knight.
At first, he didn't think he could
do the whole helping people approach.
But as soon as he got started,
well, even I was impressed.
I can't be sure, but I think deep down,
part of him wanted this all along.
Using his abilities to give
people their happy endings.
Or at least that's how it seems to me.
Saying it all aloud, I believe Operation
White Knight is the best approach for him.
If he wants the most awesome marriage,
he's gotta find a partner
the most awesome way!
No one knows their way around relationships
better than a marriage, Swindler.
We are the Mitsubi Six!
Fear the Slothmasters!
Hopefully nothing bad happens
before we can reach him Huh?
If blood's gonna stain these
claws, Hitman, I'll die!
I'm sure the other masters
are attacking him as we speak.
Close combat doesn't seem
like his strongest suit.
Won't this be all for nothing if he ends
up dying before finding someone to marry?
I wouldn't worry.
I took the liberty of hiring
muscle in case things went south.
Damn it.
I should have quoted a
higher estimate for this job.
None of them are particularly strong,
but they excel in close-quarters combat.
The groundwater will run out
before their stamina does.
I can only fight while
conserving water for so long.
Water Master, lend me a hand.
I don't work for you, so I
don't have to take orders.
Just listen.
I'm asking for your help.
Here comes the poison jab!
Everybody clear out!
Maintain visual on the target!
We'll be fine if we keep our distance!
It should disperse in no time!
We already knew he would counter
with this sort of attack.
The poison is forcing
its way into our lungs!
Mr. Gato.
Obviously mist is one of my tools,
but don't make unreasonable demands.
Commanding me to use it to control
your poison is crossing the line.
Don't ever do that again.
I expect advance notice
before future joint ventures.
Sorry.
Time is money, so let's pick up the pace.
Hey, Water Master.
Thanks for what you did.
You were a lifesaver back there.
For a fun surprise, I called in
a cutie who's tough as nails.
The two of them should have met up by now.
With Miss Arashiyama here,
won't that cause problems?
I must keep my mind clear.
Abandon all hope, ye who enter here.
Accepting your fate is the
only way to die peacefully.
Unfortunately, the test subject they
locked in beside me won't last long.
She's already at death's door.
As long as I stay quiet and do as I'm
told, I can avoid any more suffering.
One has to justly let go.
Either you keep your
sanity and die like a man,
or go insane and perish like an animal.
Once they imprison you here, that's
the one freedom you have left.
That woman's got three days to live, Tops.
I only have a few hours left.
This is it.
Pretty low, sending children
to spy on our network.
You should have known better, kid.
Adults can be cruel.
We can't have some rat girl sticking
her whiskers in our operations.
I call this Senzo Hashoku.
This little pill not only cleanses your
insides, it gives you a killer high.
A real two-birds-one-stone-wonder drug.
Your organs belong to us now.
After my brother disappeared, I
knew I couldn't turn down the job.
What was I thinking?
I can't do this!
I'm not ready to die yet!
I wish I'd turned the association
down even when they insisted!
No, even more than that.
I wish I'd never been
born a master at all.
How did you find our hideout?
You left us no choice.
We've got to perforate you.
Take him out!
What?
They're the Guardians of Order!
Why would they hire one
of the five families?
That's not how the game is played!
You saved my life! Thank you!
I just did the job I was told to do.
Wow!
He's so cool!
In that moment, I made a vow.
Since he was my knight in shining armor,
I'd be his number one fan for life!
I said that.
But deep down, I knew the truth.
In those days, Gero was
all kinds of messed up.
And I was just some jerk who
only saw what I wanted to see.
I want to risk it.
but then he reached out and helped me
again not because someone told him he
had to like before this time he wanted
to he matured into an amazing person
well here I am still being useless you in
hamster master I say we
go kick the beast clans
ass together I have
to be a beast I'm gonna
give it everything I've
I refuse to let him down!
Ratty rat rat rat rat!
Ratty rat!
All you hammies and ratties get
in position around the cages!
Here we go!
Come!
Modified Bloodline++?
Hammy Rat Network is online!
Listen up, everyone!
My name is Kimi Arashiyama,
the Hamster Master.
Hey, what do you say?
We bust out of this joint!
Don't be creepy, oh, say that boys
Oh, don't be creepy, oh, say that boys
Ah,
I'll be creepy, oh, make a voice
can't see what I'm talking about
The problem is that I'm looking at
I want to feel the growth of my growth
That's why I'm dying I
love you, baby I love you,
baby
Criss cross, a little drop,
that's cross-sanguination
It's almost time we got this
party started, wouldn't you say?
Hyako?
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Why?
I'm just your average
everyday marriage lawyer.
Maybe we should serve
while doing at our cafe.
Next time, offering.